hometheaterreview.com 2019-04-06

# HomeTheaterReview.com Network Privacy Policy & Terms of Use

**Privacy**

Del Colliano Enterprises, Inc., producer of HomeTheaterReview.com and its related content and service sites, is firmly committed to respecting the privacy of our readers, those people who visit and/or use our web property. At HomeTheaterReview.com we appreciate your readership and value your personal privacy. We respect the personal nature of the information you provide us on our web site and acknowledge the importance of protecting this information. By using or accessing HomeTheaterReview.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. The following policy explains how your personal information will be treated. Please check back periodically, as these policies may change from time to time; however, our fundamental commitment to protecting reader privacy will not change.

Minors; COPPA Compliance

Our promotions are not open to those under 18 years of age.  We do not knowingly market to or solicit information from persons under 18.  We do not knowingly collect, solicit or store personal information, even in aggregate, from anyone under the age of 18 or knowingly allow such persons to enter our promotions. If you are under 18, please do not attempt to register on our site, enter our promotions or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a person under age 18, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a minor under 18, please contact us at **privacy at hometheaterreview.com**. 

Registration

You may view and use many portions of our site anonymously and without user registration. User registration and sign-in are required under the following circumstances: 1) newsletter subscription; 2) online sweepstakes and promotions entries; 3) in order to make suggestions or proposed contributions to our "Wiki" style content; 4) in order to participate on site forums; and 5) in order to post comments or critiques of other user's comments on any site articles or other content. Except as otherwise specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, all site user registration information shall be kept private.

Newsletter and Database Information; Actions You Can Take

HomeTheaterReview.com offers a free weekly newsletter to subscribers listed in its newsletter database. When you sign up for our newsletter, you be given the chance to opt into receiving special offers from our advertising partners.  If at any time you wish to be removed from either the newsletter or advertiser databases, you may opt out by using the automated link found on our website and on all correspondence to you, in order to remove yourself from our database. Please note that by using this automated link, you will be removed from our database within 24 hours. Please be aware that if you thereafter enter any of our sweepstakes or re-subscribe to the newsletter, you will be added back to our database. Even if you remove yourself from the database, you are still eligible to remain entered into and win any currently running sweepstakes that you have entered prior to opting out.  If you would like to change or update your current data (e.g., your e-mail address) or use parameters in our database, simply log into your user account to make the edit yourself or  e-mail **webmaster @ hometheaterreview.com** and we'll take quick action.

If you are having problems removing yourself from our database via the automated link, please send an e-mail to **webmaster @ hometheaterreview.com**

and we'll promptly manually remove you from our database.

Flames, e-mails with profanity, threats or other abusive content will be deleted, reported to the appropriate authorities or ISPs, or referred to our legal counsel for appropriate action. Please remember, we only want people in our database who are interested in and excited about our newsletter and related correspondence.

What We Do With Sweepstakes Information

HomeTheaterReview.com collects contact information (e.g., e-mail addresses, phone numbers and street addresses) and demographic information (e.g., zip code, age or income level) for each monthly contest. This information is provided to the sponsor company that is running each sweepstakes that you have actually entered.  We also use this information to contact the reader if he or she is a contest winner. This information may be used by HomeTheaterReview.com (or our sponsors) to notify viewers of products and/or services that may be of interest to them. This is sometimes done through our weekly e-mail newsletter further discussed below. You may choose to tell us that you do not wish to have your information used as a basis for further contact with you, and we will respect your wishes; you may also update your personal information in our database. On occasion, summaries and aggregations of profile data collected on contest entry forms are shared with our advertisers and other partners.

Surveys

HomeTheaterReview.com occasionally offers online surveys to our readers.  Online surveys are used so that we can gather information to better serve you.  We may share summaries and aggregations of profile data collected on surveys with advertisers and other partners.  You are not required to complete online surveys, sweepstakes or promotions.

Site Visit Information

We gather information on site activity, such as the reader's domain name/IP address (e.g., whether the reader is logged on from netscape.com or yale.edu), referral data (e.g., the address of the last URL a reader visited prior to clicking through to our site), and browser/platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform) using Google Analytics. We use this information on an aggregate, anonymous basis, to improve site content and target advertising. We also may disclose aggregated information (for example, the percentage of our readers visiting the product reviews section) to third parties. When we do present such aggregated site activity to third parties, no one will be able to identify you or contact you.

Links

Our site contains links to other sites, such as those of our advertisers.  We provide these links solely as a convenience to our readers.  Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites, including the accuracy, completeness, reliability or suitability of the information. We encourage our readers to be aware when they leave our site and strongly recommend that you read the privacy policies of such other sites, as such other sites may collect information about you. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by HomeTheaterReview.com.

Information Requests

As a courtesy to our site visitors, the HomeTheaterReview.com website offers an information request form or link at the bottom of each of our "Brands" pages so that site visitors may request additional information or ask specific questions about a product. These communications are routed to the staff of HomeTheaterReview.com who will either provide the requested information or, at our discretion, forward the inquiry to the product manufacturer for a direct response.

Third Party Advertising

Advertisements that appear on HomeTheaterReview.com are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. HomeTheaterReview.com does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your personal information unless you choose to share it with them.

**Interest-Based Advertising**

Some of the ads you see on this web site are tailored to your interests and based on your activity online or in the applications on your mobile device. This type of ad tailoring -- sometimes called "interest-based" or "online behavioral" advertising -- is enabled through various technologies, including browser cookies, mobile advertising identifiers as well as other non-cookie technologies. To help protect your privacy, we are committed to providing you transparency and choice for these activities. For more information and to opt-out of interest-based advertising, please visit: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org/](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/)

Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information stored directly on the computer that you are using.  Cookies can contain a variety of information, such as a simple count of how often you visit a Web Site or information that allows the customization of a Web Site for your use.  The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry. If you click on one of our banner ads, you may get cookies from our advertisers that allow the tracking of your response to our advertisements.  These cookies do not identify you personally and are solely for the purpose of assisting us in measuring the effectiveness of advertisements placed on our site. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by HomeTheaterReview.com and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

Advertisers on HomeTheaterReview.com may elect to use third party advertising companies to serve ads on our Web site, and in these instances may use a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs/action tags/pixel tags) to better manage advertising on our site. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. Clear gifs may ping or alert the advertiser's server about the online movements of Web users. For instance, advertisers may place a clear gif allowing them to recognize an existing cookie on your browser if from the same service. The main difference between cookies and clear gifs is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Please keep in mind, we do not have access to any information collected by these clear gifs nor additional information they may be tied to by the advertiser.

Comments and Forums

Any information you disclose voluntarily on our comments pages or in any forums we may develop in the future becomes public information. We cannot control the actions of our site users and advise you to use your discretion in sharing information about yourself on the Internet. All information sharing is optional and done at your own risk. Privacy is a very personal matter and we encourage you to be careful and responsible when disclosing personal information online.

Revisions

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within thirty (30) days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you through notice on our home page and registered users shall be notified by email. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you.

Contact Us

Any and all questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to **privacy @ hometheaterreview.com**.  You may also contact us by mail at 9701 Wilshire, 10th Floor, Beverly Hills, CA  90212.

**Terms of Use**

Please read these Terms of Use before using this website. By continuing to use HomeTheaterReview.com, you agree to abide by the conditions of this website as set forth below:

General Terms

Welcome to HomeTheaterReview.com.  We reserve the right to change the Terms of Use or to modify any features of this website at any time. Any changes shall apply as soon as they are posted. The most current version of the Terms of Use can be viewed at any time at HomeTheaterReview.com. 

Copyright Provisions

This website (including, without limitation, text, wiki, photographs, graphics, video and audio content) is protected by copyright as a collective work or compilation under the copyright laws of the United States and other countries, and HomeTheaterReview.com has rights therein. All individual articles, videos, content and other elements comprising this website are also copyrighted works, and HomeTheaterReview.com (subject to the rights of its sponsors, licensors and licensees under applicable agreements, understandings and arrangements) has rights therein. You must abide by all additional copyright notices or restrictions contained in this website. 

You shall be solely responsible for your own submissions and the consequences of posting or publishing them. In connection with each of your submissions, you affirm, represent, and/or warrant that you own or have the necessary licenses, rights, consents, and permissions to use and authorize HomeTheaterReview.com to use all copyright or other proprietary rights in and to any and all such submissions. In furtherance of the foregoing, you agree that you will not: (i) submit material that is copyrighted, protected by trade secret or otherwise subject to third party proprietary rights, including privacy and publicity rights, unless you are the owner of such rights or have permission from their rightful owner to post the material and to grant HomeTheaterReview.com all of the rights granted herein; (ii) publish falsehoods or misrepresentations that could damage HomeTheaterReview.com or any third party; (iii) submit material that is unlawful, obscene, defamatory, libelous, threatening, pornographic, harassing, hateful, racially or ethnically offensive, or encourages conduct that would be considered a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability, violate any law, or is otherwise inappropriate; or (iv) post advertisements or solicitations of business.

HomeTheaterReview.com reserves the right to remove or not publish submissions without prior notice.

Site Registration

Users who are 18 years of age or older and wish to comment on articles published on HomeTheaterReview.com can register for a user account. When registering, the user will receive a confirmation link to confirm their email address. This double opt-in process is done to ensure that only users who wish to become HomeTheaterReview.com registered users are entered into our database. The user selects his/her own password and we recommend keeping that password in a secure location.  If the user forgets his or her password, Home Theater Review can automatically send a password reminder email, provided that the user answers the "security" question correctly (i.e., What is your favorite color?). This security question will be asked during the sign-up process.  Users will also have the opportunity to opt into HomeTheaterReview.com's weekly email list as well as the third party Sponsors' email list. This information is not sold and all emails are sent directly by HomeTheaterReview.com. Clear opt-out instructions are located at the bottom of each email.

If a user wishes to no longer be a registered HomeTheaterReview.com user, he or she can delete their account by sending an email to **webmaster at hometheaterreview.com** with the subject header "Delete my account" and the user name he or she registered with. We will do our best to remove the user's account within 2 business days.

Comments, Forums, User Opinion Posts (User Generated Content)

At the end of many of HomeTheaterReview.com's articles, users will have the option to post comments. These posts are moderated by HomeTheaterReview.com and we will make our best effort to ensure that users to not use profanity or attempt to defame or slander anyone. If you see a post that you feel is in bad-taste or is defamatory, we urge you to notify us immediately by sending us an email to **webmaster @ hometheaterreview.com** with a link to the article, the name of the user who posted the message and what the first few words of the post are so we can quickly find it and determine using our reasonable editorial discretion if the post needs to be removed. We believe in the freedom for users to express their opinions however we will not tolerate threats, profanity or slander.  We cannot guarantee that we will remove all posts that are brought to our attention.

Suggested Wiki Contributions (User Suggested Content)

As a service to our readers, HomeTheaterReview.com provides "wiki enyclopedia" style information about the products and concepts we discuss on HomeTheaterReview.com. If a site visitor reads what they believe to be inaccurate or out-of-date information, we encourage such site viewer to become a HomeTheaterReview.com registered user and submit a "wiki" update to us. We may or may not make the suggested change and we do not provide notification if any suggestion was incorporated, however if we do in fact use the contributed information, in whole or in part, to make an edit or update to a particular wiki, the user who made the suggestion will get credited under their HomeTheaterReview.com user name in the "Contributors" section on that page, below the title. If a user has made a suggested change to a wiki, we suggest that user bookmark or create an RSS feed for that article so he or she will be notified when it is updated.

DMCA Take Down Notices

If you are a copyright owner or agent thereof and believe that any HomeTheaterReview.com content infringes upon your copyright, please submit notice, pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (17 U.S.C. § 512(c)) to our Copyright Agent with the following information: (i) an electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright; (ii) a description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed; (iii) the URL of the location containing the material that you claim is infringing; (iv) your address, telephone number, and email address; (v) a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; (vi) a statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your Notice is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner's behalf.

Our Copyright Agent can be reached as follows: 

By mail: HomeTheaterReview.com / Attn: Copyright Agent / 9701 Wilshire, 10th Floor / Beverly Hills, CA  90212

By phone: 310.860.9988

By email: copyrightagent @ hometheaterreview.com

Please note that attachments cannot be accepted at the email address for security reasons. Accordingly, any notification of infringement submitted electronically with an attachment will not be received or processed.

RSS Feeds and Other Dynamic Data Feeds

Users who would like to be notified when various sections or pages on HomeTheaterReview.com are updated are encouraged to use our dynamic RSS 2.0 content feeds. Users may include the headline and the first few lines of copy of our articles on their RSS feed page however when linking to the remaining copy of an article, the link must drive the user to the full page on HomeTheaterReview.com

All of the content is property of HomeTheaterReview.com and we do not warranty the feeds and provide no support for users. For more information on RSS please visit this link below

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/RSS_(file_format)

Thank you for visiting HomeTheaterReview.com.

Privacy Policy & Terms of Use were updated on January 22, 2019.

© 2019, Del Colliano Enterprises, Inc.

* * *
